Open the display settings in 2025.0
In the 2025.0 version, the display settings function has been added, so the software will not record the previous display option changes.
How to preserve the default display settings?
When we open the file, the 3D window will randomly display the texture surface, and display the basic line, internal line, thickness, and other information.
First, in the 3D window, change the texture surface to the thick texture surface display.
And hide the internal line and the basic line.
And hide the thickness, thinness.
In addition to the display settings in the 3D window, you can also change the display settings in the 2D window.
You can choose to display or hide clothing information, version information, etc.
For example, display or hide version name, logo.
You can also change the different clothing rendering types.
After the settings are complete, select the virtual model and delete the model.
Select all the panels and delete the panels.
Save this blank file.
After saving, select the settings in the software and define the user name.
Select default file, project, project file.
Change the default file to the file just saved.
The 3D window will prompt you to restart the program to change the application.
Restart the software to check the settings.
Open any clothing, and match a virtual model.
You can see that the display of this file is set to the settings just saved.
And press the Go button to start the program.
And now the program starts to load.